fleshlight.com 2015-12-14

# Fleshlight privacy Policy

This website (the “Site”) is the property of Interactive Life Forms, LLC, a Texas Limited Liability Company, whose primary offices are located at 7000 Burleson Road, Building C, Austin, TX 78744 and Fleshlight Canada Distribution, ULC, whose primary offices are located at 2525 Dunwin Drive, Unit 2, Mississauga, Ontario L5L 1R9, as applicable, (collectively, “ILF”, “we”, or “us”). ILF respects the privacy of those who access and/or use the Site (“You”, “Your”, “User”, or collectively “Users”) and is committed to protecting the privacy of the personally identifiable information we collect from You as You access and/or use the Site via the internet, the world wide web, mobile networks, or any other communication methods now known or in the future developed.

THIS PRIVACY POLICY SET FORTH BELOW (THE “PRIVACY POLICY”) HEREBY INCORPORATES BY REFERENCE THE TERMS OF USE OF THE SITE AND IS INCORPORATED INTO AND IS SUBJECT TO THE TERMS THEREIN. YOUR USE OF THE SITE AND ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION YOU PROVIDE THROUGH THE SITE ARE SUBJECT AT ALL TIME TO THE PRIVACY POLICY AND THE TERMS OF USE. BY USING THE SITE, YOU ARE ACCEPTING THE PRIVACY POLICY AND THE TERMS OF USE. 

* **The Information That The Site Collects**

  1. _Automatically Collected Information_

When You access the Site, we may send one or more cookies to Your computer. A cookie is a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters that a website stores on Your computer that Your browser provides to a website each time You access the website. Use of cookies is very common on the Internet. We use these cookies to identify prior Users and track usage of the Site. We do not use cookies to personally identify Users of the Site. You can remove these cookies and modify Your browser’s settings to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify You when a cookie is sent. Please review Your web browser’s “Help” file to learn the proper way to modify Your cookie settings. 

In addition, like many websites, when You access the Site, we may automatically record certain information from Your system by using different types of other common Internet technology. This automatically collected information may include Your Internet Protocol address (“IP Address”), a unique device or User ID, version of software installed, system type, the content and pages that You access on the Site, and the dates and times that You visit Site. 

  2. _Personally Identifiable Information_

ILF only collects personally identifiable information that is voluntarily provided to us by a User. 

* **The Way We Use This Information**

  1. _Automatically Collected Information_

ILF uses cookies and other automatically collected information to identify prior Users, to track usage of the Site, and for analytical purposes to help us improve the Site and our business in general. We may on occasion provide this information to an affiliate or third party to assist us in providing these functions. 

  2. _Personally Identifiable Information_

The personally identifiable information that Users voluntarily provide to ILF may be used by ILF and our Affiliates for administrative purposes; for authentication purposes; to properly operate, maintain, and provide You with the features and functionality of the Site; to customize and personalize features for You and otherwise enrich your experience when using the Site; to present You with promotions, advertisement, and opportunities We believe may be of interest to You; to enable our affiliates and to assist us in operating, maintaining, and providing our Services and products to You; to enable us to carry out our obligations arising from any contracts/subscriptions entered into with You; to notify You about changes to the Privacy Policy or the Terms of Service, Site, or Site (if we deem it appropriate); to investigate and help prevent potentially unlawful activity or activities that threaten the integrity of the Site, ILF Content, or ILF Technology; to investigate allegations of fraud or violations of the Terms; to enforce or apply our rights under the Terms; and/or to protect the rights, property, or safety of any of our Users or others; to improve the quality and design of the Site and to create new features, promotions, functionality, and services by storing, tracking, and analyzing your preferences and trends.

  3. _Alternative Use of Personally Identifiable Information_

Although consent for the use or disclosure of personally identifiable information will usually be obtained at the time of collection, there may be occasions where consent is sought after the personally identifiable information has been collected (but before use). If ILF intends to use personally identifiable information for a purpose other than what was identified at the time the personally identifiable information was collected, then we will obtain Your prior consent to that additional use unless it is for a situation where consent can be implied through Your actions with us.

* **Security of Information**

ILF maintains our systems in accordance with commercially reasonable industry standards to preserve the integrity and security of Your personally identifiable information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information You Transmit through the Site, and You do so at Your own risk. Once we receive Your transmission of information, we make commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems including contractual and/or other safeguards to ensure that affiliates, related companies or third party service providers (“Third Parties”) provide a comparable level of protection for your personally identifiable information. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. “Perfect security" does not exist on the Internet, and You use the Site at Your own risk. If You have reason to believe that Your information stored with us is no longer secure, you must immediately notify us of the problem by contacting us as set out on our Site.

ILF has safeguards to protect personally identifiable information against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification, regardless of the format in which the information is held. Personally identifiable information will be safeguarded by physical measures (locking filing cabinets, restricting access to offices), organizational measures (employee training, limiting access on a necessity basis) and technological measures (Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology passwords, firewalls and encryption). Some records, including older records, may be stored at an offsite storage facility, in either paper or electronic format. Where records are stored with off-site storage facilities, ILF uses contractual or other means to ensure that your privacy rights are protected. As a result, personally identifiable information may be subject to legal requirements of foreign countries as applicable, such as the requirement to disclose personally identifiable information to foreign governments.

* **Limiting Use, Disclosure, and Retention**

ILF always uses contractual or other safeguards to ensure protection of personally identifiable information and such information will be used and disclosed only for the purpose for which it was collected or as required by law, except with the consent of the individual. When personally identifiable information is no longer required to fulfill the purpose for which it was collected, it will be destroyed, erased or made anonymous, provided there are no legal requirements for its continued retention should the same be possible.

Access to personally identifiable information is limited to ILF employees with a business need to know and Third Parties who require access for business purposes. From time to time, ILF will disclose personally identifiable information to others, including to affiliated entities or unrelated companies that carry out certain responsibilities on behalf of ILF. ILF takes necessary steps to ensure that the affiliated entities or unrelated companies do not use or disclose personally identifiable information for any purpose other than the specific purpose requested.

* **Accuracy**

ILF will take all reasonable efforts to ensure that personally identifiable information is accurate, complete, and up-to-date in relation to the purposes for which the personally identifiable information is to be used. 

* **Individual Access**

Access to personally identifiable information, including how we use and disclose the personally identifiable information may be obtained on written request. An individual can challenge the accuracy and completeness of their personally identifiable information and have it amended as appropriate. An individual’s written request for access to personally identifiable information will be answered within a reasonable time and at a reasonable cost. We will assist any individual who informs us that they need assistance in preparing a written request and we may require an individual to provide sufficient information to permit us to provide an account of the existence, use and disclosure of personally identifiable information. Any such identifying information shall be used only for this purpose. If an individual successfully establishes the inaccuracy or incompleteness of personally identifiable information such personally identifiable information will be amended to ensure that it is accurate. If a challenge to the accuracy of personally identifiable information is not resolved to the satisfaction of the individual, we will document the content of the challenge. The amended personally identifiable information or the existence of the unresolved challenge, as the case may be, may be transmitted to affiliated entities or unrelated companies having access to the information in question. Requests for access to personally identifiable information we hold about an individual may be refused if permitted or required by law. In such a case, the reasons for denying access will be provided to the individual upon request which reasons may include: information that contains references to other individuals or contains confidential commercial information which cannot be redacted from the file; information collected in the course of investigating a breach of an agreement or in the course of a formal dispute resolution process; and information that is subject to solicitor-client privilege. 

* **Updates to this Privacy Policy**

ILF reserves the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy. If this Privacy Policy materially changes, ILF will take reasonable measures to notify you of these changes, including posting a copy of the revised Privacy Policy on the Site. Your continued consent to our collection, use and disclosure practices following notification of any material change and/or your continued access to the Site following the posting of any changes to this Privacy Policy shall constitute your acceptance of such changes. 

* **Lost or Stolen Information.**

You are solely responsible for any and all use of Customer Account, Fleshlight Videos Account and/or Forum Membership. You are solely responsible for the confidentiality and security of Customer Account, Fleshlight Videos Account and/or Forum Membership password and log-in information. You agree to immediately notify ILF of any actual or suspected breach of security or unauthorized use of Your Customer Account, Fleshlight Videos Account and/or Forum Membership. 

* **Children**

ILF DOES NOT SELL PRODUCTS OR SERVICES FOR PURCHASE BY CHILDREN. YOU MUST BE AT LEAST 18 YEARS OF AGE OR 21 IN SOME AREAS, TO ACCESS OR USE THE SITE AT ANY TIME OR IN ANY MANNER. BY USING THE SITE, YOU REPRESENT THAT YOU ARE VOLUNTARILY CHOOSING TO VIEW AND ACCESS SEXUALLY-ORIENTED ADULT CONTENT FOR YOUR OWN PERSONAL USE, YOU ARE THE LEGAL AGE IN YOUR JURISDICTION TO VIEW SUCH MATERIAL, YOU WON’T ALLOW ANY PERSON UNDER THE LEGAL AGE TO VIEW SUCH MATERIAL OR PEOPLE WHO MAY BE OFFENDED BY SUCH MATERIAL TO VIEW ANY ADULT CONTENT FROM THIS SITE, YOU HAVE NOT BEEN PREVIOUSLY SUSPENDED FROM THE SITE, YOU ARE NOT ACCESSING THIS SITE FROM ANY MUNICPALITY, CITY, STATE, PROVINCE, COUNTRY, OR OTHER JURISDICTION WHERE VIEWING SUCH CONTENT IS PROHIBITED BY LAW, AND THAT THE ADULT CONTENT YOU HAVE CHOSEN TO ACCESS AND/OR TRANSMIT FROM THIS SITE IS WITHIN THE CONTEMPORARY STANDARDS OF ACCEPTANCE AND TOLERANCE OF YOUR COMMUNITY FOR SUCH MATERIALS. 

PROTECTING THE PRIVACY OF YOUNG CHILDREN IS ESPECIALLY IMPORTANT. FOR THAT REASON, ILF DOES NOT KNOWINGLY COLLECT OR MAINTAIN PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION FROM PERSONS UNDER 13 YEARS-OF-AGE. IF ILF LEARNS THAT PERSONALLY-IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION OF PERSONS LESS THAN 13-YEARS-OF-AGE HAS BEEN COLLECTED ON OR THROUGH THE SITE, THEN WE WILL TAKE THE APPROPRIATE STEPS TO DELETE THIS INFORMATION. 

IF YOU ARE THE PARENT OR LEGAL GUARDIAN OF A CHILD UNDER 13 WHO HAS PROVIDED US WITH PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION, THEN PLEASE EMAIL US TO HAVE THAT INFORMATION DELETED IMMEDIATELY. 

The following are some resources that may help parents and legal guardians in monitoring and limiting children’s access to certain types of material on the internet. While ILF does not endorse these products, we provide information about them as a public service. 

  * OnGuard Online
  * WiredSafety
  * Netsmartz.org
  * The Child Safety Network
  * Control Kids
  * Cyber Sitter
  * Net Nanny

* **Links to Third Party Sites**

The Site may include links or references to other websites or services (“Linked Sites”). Linked Sites are provided for Your convenience and information only. Please be aware that ILF is not responsible for the privacy practices of such sites. We encourage You to be aware of when You leave the Site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by ILF through the Site. 

* **Events Outside Of Ordinary Business Practices**

IN CONNECTION WITH AN EVENT OUTSIDE OF ILF’S ORDINARY BUSINESS PRACTICES, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO A SALE, MERGER, CONSOLIDATION, CHANGE IN CONTROL, TRANSFER OF SUBSTANTIAL ASSETS, REORGANIZATION, OR LIQUIDATION, ILF RESERVES THE RIGHT TO TRANSFER, SELL, OR ASSIGN THE INFORMATION THAT WE HAVE COLLECTED FROM USERS. 

ILF ALSO RESERVES THE RIGHT TO DISCLOSE USER INFORMATION IN THE GOOD-FAITH BELIEF THAT IT IS REQUIRED TO DO SO PURSUANT TO JUDICIAL OR OTHER GOVERNMENTAL SUBPOENAS, WARRANTS, OR ORDERS, OR TO DISCLOSE SUCH DATA TO A GOVERNMENTAL INSTITUTION THAT HAS ASSERTED ITS LAWFUL AUTHORITY TO OBTAIN THE INFORMATION. ILF ALSO RESERVES THE RIGHT TO DISCLOSE USER INFORMATION THAT WE BELIEVE, IN GOOD FAITH, IS APPROPRIATE OR NECESSARY: TO TAKE PRECAUTIONS AGAINST LIABILITY; TO PROTECT ILF FROM FRAUDULENT, ABUSIVE, OR UNLAWFUL USES; TO INVESTIGATE AND DEFEND OURSELVES AGAINST THIRD-PARTY CLAIMS OR ALLEGATIONS; TO ASSIST GOVERNMENT ENFORCEMENT AGENCIES; TO PROTECT THE SECURITY OR INTEGRITY OF THE SITE; OR TO PROTECT THE RIGHTS, PROPERTY, OR PERSONAL SAFETY OF ILF, OUR USERS, OR OTHERS. 

* **NON-U.S. USERS**

FOR USERS VISITING THE SITE FROM THE EUROPEAN ECONOMIC AREA, CANADA OR OTHER NON-U.S. TERRITORIES, PLEASE NOTE THAT ANY DATA YOU VOLUNTARILY PROVIDED US WILL BE TRANSFERRED OUTSIDE THE EUROPEAN ECONOMIC AREA, CANADA OR SUCH OTHER NON-U.S. TERRITORY FOR USE BY ILF FOR ANY OF THE PURPOSES DESCRIBED HEREIN. 

* **Change in Privacy Policy**

By using the Site, you are accepting the Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use. ILF reserves the right, in our sole discretion, to modify, alter, or otherwise update this Privacy Policy at any time. Such modifications shall be effective immediately upon posting. You are responsible for regularly reviewing the Privacy Policy. Your continued access to and/or use of the Site constitutes Your agreement to all such modifications. 

* **Google Analytics**

Through our provider, Google Analytics, data is collected about use of our sites. We will not provide Google Analytics with your name, credit card number, birthday, phone number, email address and address information. We assign a random number to your usage so that Google Analytics can identify unique users of our sites. However, Google Analytics cannot associate that number with your personally identifiable information. We recognize that you may prefer to limit or eliminate the data that Google Analytics collects about your use of our sites. Google Analytics does provide an “Opt-out” option. Directions can be found at:[http:/2015-holiday-(bf/cm)-combos//www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html](http://2015-holiday-%28bf/cm\)-combos//www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html). 

* **Your California Privacy Rights**

California residents who have an established business relationship with ILF may choose to opt out of ILF disclosing personal information about them to third parties for marketing purposes. From time to time, we may share your personal information with carefully screened companies that offer products or services that we believe you may enjoy. If you do not want us to share your personal information with such third parties, please send us your name, email address, street address and phone number to [http:/2015-holiday-(bf/cm)-combos//support.fleshlight.com/index.php?_m=tickets&_a=submit](http://2015-holiday-%28bf/cm\)-combos//support.fleshlight.com/index.php?_m=tickets&_a=submit). Your opt out request will be processed within 30 days of the date it was received. 

* **Visitors From Outside the US**

If you are a visitor from outside the United States, please be aware that our company and servers are located in the United States. You hereby consent to your information being processed in the United States as set forth in this Privacy Policy. 

* **Unsubscribe**

ILF will communicate with You only if you want to hear from us. If You prefer not to receive promotional information, such as information about special offers, you can let us know by following the "opt out" instructions provided in promotional electronic mail sent to you.

If you ask us to remove your name and address from our promotional lists, we will maintain your name in a "do not contact" file in order to honor your request. It may take up to eight (8) weeks to process your request, during which period you may continue to receive communications from ILF.

* **Contact Information**

Interactive Life Forms, LLC   
7000 Burleson Road, Building C  
Austin, TX 78744 USA  
Attention: General Counsel Phone: [+1 (888) 804-4453](tel:+18888044453), from 10am to 10pm CST 

If you have a privacy question about our website or would like to change or remove any of your information, please submit a Ticket here: [http:/2015-holiday-(bf/cm)-combos//support.fleshlight.com/index.php?_m=tickets&_a=submit](http://2015-holiday-%28bf/cm\)-combos//support.fleshlight.com/index.php?_m=tickets&_a=submit).

All written complaints will be investigated and if ILF determines a complaint to be justified, we will take all appropriate measures, including, if necessary, amending our Privacy Policy, policies and/or practices. A complainant will be advised of the outcome of the investigation regarding their complaint.

For users in Canada, we encourage the use of our internal information and resolution process to resolve a complaint however an individual may also seek advice from the Office of the Privacy Commissioner of Canada at [1.800.282.1376](tel:+18002821376) or [info@privcom.gc.ca](mailto:info@privcom.gc.ca) and, if appropriate, file written complaint with that office.
